http://www.merinews.com/privacy_policy.jsp

Submit :
News						                    						Photos						                    Just						In                    						Debate						Topic                    						Latest						News                    Articles                    Local						News                    Blog						Posts                    						Pictures                    Reviews                    Recipes
New to merinews?
WORLD
INDIA
SPORTS
BUSINESS
TECHNOLOGY
ENTERTAINMENT
LIFESTYLE
REVIEWS
INTERVIEWS					 LOCAL
Sign In | Register
Sign Out
Merinews Picks
World leaders greet Muslims on commencement of the holy month of Ramadan
The Prime Minister of India, Narendra Modi has greeted the people on the start of holy month of Ramazan and stated, "Greetings on..
Dr. Lalit Kishore
more...
Mississippi shooter leaves 8.. World leaders greet Muslims on.. US Secretary of State Tillerson.. Alzheimer's on the rise, is it..
Debate 							        Paris attacks will have a major fallback on Syrian refugees seeking asylum in Europe
Agree :
85.71								%
Disagree :
14.29								%
More Categories
Business Politics Others
Merinews Picks
Bhagat Singh's pistol put up on display at BSF Museum in Hussainiwala
The avenging pistol – epic .32 mm bore Colt automatic pistol of Bhagat Singh – which he had used for killing British officer John..
HARISH DIDO
more...
CBI takes custody of murder.. Youth4Swaraj's Drought Duty.. Heavy showers in Bangalore.. PM Modi embarks upon four-nation..
Debate 							        Demonetisation of Rs.500, Rs.1000 a step in right direction
Agree :
75.0								%
Disagree :
25.0								%
More Categories
Society and Culture Politics Business NRI Local News
Merinews Picks
Live Update: Pro Kabaddi League 2017 auction
Day 2 of auction is underway for Pro Kabaddi League Season 5 which starts from July 2017. The fifth edition of the League shall see..
sam bansal
more...
Live Update: Pro Kabaddi League.. IPL 10 Final Preview: MI V/s RPS.. IPL 10 Prediction: Qualifier 2 –.. IPL 10 Preview: Eliminator – KKR..
Debate 							        IPL should be given a break!
Agree :
44.44								%
Disagree :
55.56								%
More Categories
Cricket Football Tennis Racing Other Sports Hockey Kabaddi
Merinews Picks
How SMEs are benefiting from the internet?
In recent past we have seen a surge in internet penetration in India. The reasons are multiple like the ambitious Digital India..
Rohit Sinha
more...
Post-demonetisation banks have.. Ola declares loss of Rs 2313.. How SMEs are benefiting from the.. Talwandi Sabo thermal plant shut..
Debate 							        Reliance taking control over the Network18 group is not a good news for news industry
Agree :
66.67								%
Disagree :
33.33								%
More Categories
SME Corporate Economy Mutual Funds Global Markets Personal Finance Others Start Ups
Merinews Picks
New bacteria discovered on filters of International Space Station named after late Dr Kalam, former President of India
The National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) in the United States has named new bacteria found on the filters of the..
Dr. Lalit Kishore
more...
New bacteria discovered on.. Google's new Android O beta now.. NASA to launch world's lightest.. Google doodle of today..
Debate 							        iPhone's positioning of cheaper version(5c) will dilute the brand image of Apple
Agree :
46.67								%
Disagree :
53.33								%
More Categories
Gadget Reviews Technology News
Merinews Picks
In Pictures: Zhu Zhu – the sexy siren from China who makes her Bollywood debut in Salman's Tubelight
Popular Chinese actress Zhu Zhu is all set to make her Bollywood debut in 'Tubelight' – Salman's Eid release of the year. The..
Aakanksha Mathur
more...
In Pictures: Zhu Zhu – the sexy.. Cannes Film Festival has lost.. Final season of Game of Thrones.. Hey, did you notice Shah Rukh in..
Debate 							        Protests against Aamir Khan's PK are unjustified
Agree :
54.55								%
Disagree :
45.45								%
More Categories
Video Games Television Movies Music
Merinews Picks
Hoan Kiem Lake in Central Hanoi is a must visit for tourists to Vietnam
While in the capital city of Vietnam, Hanoi, a visit to the Hoan Kiem Lake is a must. The lake is centrally located and is one of..
Dr. Lalit Kishore
more...
Suspense finally ends as CBSE.. Hoan Kiem Lake in Central Hanoi.. Ramadan Kareem: The Islamic holy.. Destinations: A visit to Udaipur..
Debate 							        No harm if students listen to PM Narendra Modi's Teacher's Day speech
Agree :
56.25								%
Disagree :
43.75								%
More Categories
Travel Astrology Food Spirituality and Wellness Relationships Fashion and Beauty Career and Worklife Humour Personal Space Women Education Men
Merinews Picks
Book Review: "Teaching Students with Special Needs in Inclusive Settings" published by PHI Learning
The book "Teaching Students with Special Needs in Inclusive Settings" is a standard text on the topics which are equally useful for..
Dr. Lalit Kishore
more...
A Book Review: Norwegian Wood by.. Book Review: "Teaching Students.. PM Modi releases book series on.. President Pranab Mukherjee..
Debate 							        Movie Reviews serve no purpose today as most of them are paid
Agree :
70.59								%
Disagree :
29.41								%
More Categories
Book Review Movie Preview Movie Review Music Review Tele Soaps Review Others
Merinews Picks
Interview: 'It's not my film, it's all about Poorna,' says a candid Rahul Bose
Poorna Malavath is 16 now, and co-incidentally, Rahul Bose, the maker of Poorna's biopic has made his second directorial venture..
Atanu Roy
more...
Watch Video: What makes Western.. Interview: 'It's not my film,.. Dance it out and live your dream.. Science is the spirit of..
Debate 							        Should an ally blackmail the Coalition on the eve of..
Agree :
0.0								%
Disagree :
0.0								%
More Categories
Business Entertainment Sports Technology Politics Society International Personality Lifestyle
Gurgaon Bangalore Chennai Delhi Kolkata Mumbai Noida
Submit News
Events
Jobs
Columnists
Just In
Videos
Classifieds
Discount Coupons
Privacy Policy
Welcome to Merinews!
Protecting your privacy is important to Bizsol Advisors Pvt. Ltd (Bizsol Network). This policy explains the privacy while using Merinews(the website) which is part of the Bizsol Network. By using or submitting any information at Merinews you agree ot Merinews's collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this policy. If you do not agree with this policy, you may not use or submit content at Merinews.
The Information We Collect and How We Use It
The information we collect falls into two categories: (1) personal information that you provide to us when you register to use our Web site, and (2) certain anonymous information that we collect as you navigate through the merinews pages. Below is a description of each type of information we collect and how we use it:
Registration Information
Anyone may visit merinews and read its contents, but only registered users may post articles. We require users to register to encourage responsible and courteous conduct. In our registration process, we require you to provide your name, e-mail address, zip code and age. We use this information to create a unique registration profile for you, to communicate with you regarding your registration, and to verify that you are not under the age of 18. We also may ask you to provide, at your option, your address and certain demographic information. This information will help us to better understand our audience, but is not required as a condition of registering; you may decline to provide any or all such optional information. Once you register with merinews and sign in to our site, you are not anonymous to us, though you may use an assumed member name when posting to the site if you?d prefer to remain anonymous to other members of the merinews community and other visitors to the site.
E-mail Address
We require you to provide your e-mail address as part of the registration process. When you register with our site, we will send you an e-mail confirming your registration. We may use your e-mail address to send you administrative e-mails from time to time containing announcements and communications regarding the merinews service. If you do not wish to receive administrative e-mails from us, please do not register to use our site. You also may elect to receive regular newsletters or information updates from us or to receive commercial e-mails from us that advertise our services and the products or services of our advertising partners. Even if you choose to receive commercial e-mails, we will not share your e-mail address with our third-party advertisers, though we may send you advertising materials on their behalf. You may unsubscribe from such emails at any time by following the simple instructions included in each e-mail.
Browser-Level Information and Cookies
When you visit merinews, our web server automatically collects limited information about your computer configuration, such as the type of browser software you use, the operating system you're running and your IP address, and we also use ?cookies? to track which pages of our site you visit. This information does not contain your personal information or otherwise tell us who you are. We use this information to make our site as useful as we can for as many users as possible. We use cookies to prevent you from having to re-enter your log-in information each time you visit the site. If you leave merinews to visit our advertisers? Web sites, some of those advertisers also may place cookies on your computer. We don't have access to those cookies or to any information they contain, and the use and collection of your information by such third-party advertisers is governed by the advertiser?s Privacy Policy, which may be different from ours. Because cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our Web site, you can set your browser to decline cookies and can delete them from your computer. However, if you don't accept cookies, you may need to re-enter your log-in information each time you visit our site, and you may not be able to take advantage of various features on our site that are available to other visitors.
Aggregate Information Used to Serve and Target Ads
We may aggregate the information we collect from our users and use this anonymous, aggregated information to target ads on our site. (For example, we may use this information to tell advertisers the age range, gender composition, and geographic location of the audience the advertisers will be reaching.) When we aggregate your information, no specific personal information is included, and you cannot be identified from this aggregate information.
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties on our site ? for example, in a post, or on other areas of our site ? that information can be seen, collected and used by anyone who visits the site. We cannot control and therefore cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third-party use of such information. Please respect the privacy of others by not posting their personal information on our site without their permission.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet.Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy .
We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,click here
Disclosure of Information
Information about our members is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. merinews will not rent, sell, or share your personal information with unaffiliated companies or people except (1) as necessary to provide you with products or services you've requested, (2) when we have your permission, or (3) as follows:
We may disclose your personal information to trusted partners who work on behalf of merinews under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help us serve you. However, these companies are not allowed to share this information or to use it for their own purposes.
We may disclose your personal information when release is appropriate to comply with law, or to protect the rights, property or safety of members of the merinews community, other visitors to our site, our advertisers and other customers, the public, or merinews and its employees.
As our business grows we may buy or sell various assets. In the event that merinews or some or all of our assets are acquired by another company, information about our users may be among the transferred assets.
Links To Other Sites
merinews, and users who post information on merinews, may provide links to third-party Web sites whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another site, use of any information you provide is governed by the Privacy Policy of the operator of the site you're visiting.
Archiving and Storage
All merinews postings may be stored in our database, even after deletion from the site. Our web logs and other records may be stored indefinitely. In addition, search engines and other sites not affiliated with merinews may cache or archive postings from merinews, and may make such postings available for viewing on their sites. (For example, some search engines take a snapshot of each web page examined by the search engine as it crawls the web, and may cache these pages as a backup in case the original page is unavailable. Search engine users can view the cached pages simply by clicking on the ?cached? link.) We have no control over this.
Security
merinews has taken steps to protect the confidentiality of the personal information it collects from members of the merinews community. Information we gather on merinews is stored within merinews controlled databases (or databases hosted on our behalf) on servers maintained in protected environments, and we limit access to your personal information to merinews employees who we believe need to see that information to provide you with services or otherwise do their jobs. However, no physical or electronic security system is impenetrable, and we cannot guarantee the security of our servers or databases, nor can we guarantee that the information that you supply to us won't be intercepted during transmission over the Internet. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your merinews account, especially on a shared computer, by logging out when you are finished using our site.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Because the web is an evolving medium, we may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, in which case we'll post the changes to this Privacy Policy on this web site and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use the merinews Web site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified.
Getting in Touch With Us
For more information, or if you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please Contact us
Report Misconduct
If you see something on merinews that you consider inappropriate or abusive, please let us know immediately. Click on feedback and fill the form. We will review the content to see if it meets our guidelines.
Contact Us
For more information about merinews, Contact us
Not finding what you are looking for? Search here.
Some awesome recipes for Navratri..
Bigg Boss: Let's meet the winners of..
Eight most interesting things about..
Seven heroes who gave up their lives..
Follow, subscribe, or add us to your browser search.
Follow us on Facebook
Follow us on Twitter
Subscribe to RSS feeds
Add to browser Search
Archive :
Index by Date | Index by Topics | Index by Region
